<resources>
    <string name="app_name">coin Ranking</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="exchanges">Exchanges</string>
    <string name="bookmarks">BookMarks</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello exchanges fragment</string>

    <string name="action_open_drawer">Open</string>
    <string name="action_close_drawer">Close</string>
    <string name="addWhatIs">What is %s</string>

    <string name="upRate">%s</string>
    <string name="downRate">- %s %</string>
    <string name="mi_night_mode">Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="Introdution">Statistics showing an overview of Binance exchange, such as its 24h trading volume, market share and cryptocurrency listings.</string>
    <string name="about_binance"><![CDATA[Binance is a blockchain ecosystem comprising a cryptocurrency exchange, startup incubator, startup investor, and coin information provider. Binance is a highly popular exchange and allows its users to trade hundreds of cryptocurrencies, including Dogecoin, Bitcoin, and Ethereum. The exchange was founded in July 2017, by Changpeng Zhao (CZ), and was initially based in China, but was later moved out of China due to China\'s increasing regulation of cryptocurrency. The name ‘Binance’ comes from the two words ‘binary’ and ‘finance’. Binance exchange requires KYC (know-your-customer), which is the process that banks gather identifying data and contact information from current and potential customers, to prevent fraud. Binance is capable of processing 1,400,000 orders per second and supports many cryptocurrencies. Binance serves more than 15,000,000 users worldwide, operates in over 40 countries, and is based in over 180 countries & regions.]]></string>
    <string name="cryptocurrency_title">Cryptocurrency</string>

    <string name="symbol_value">%s value statistics</string>
    <string name="Desc">صعودی</string>
    <string name="Asc">نزولی</string>
    <string name="What_is_Bitcoin">Bitcoin is the first digital currency that allows users to send and receive money, without the interference of a central bank or government. Instead, a network of thousands of peers is controlling the transactions; a decentralized system.</string>
    <string name="why_btc">Bitcoin’s useful qualities (decentralized, borderless, secure) aren’t the only reason the coin is worth so much. Due to its scarcity (and it’s hard to produce), Bitcoin is often nicknamed ‘Digital Gold’, in reference to ‘classic’ physical gold. Like gold, Bitcoin also has a finite supply of coins available; there will only ever be 21 million bitcoin. And now you know why the creation of new bitcoins is also called mining.</string>
    <string name="price_to_usd">Price to USD</string>
    <string name="price_to_btc">Price to BTC</string>
    <string name="rank">Rank</string>
    <string name="_24h_volume">24h volume</string>
    <string name="market_cap">Market cap</string>
    <string name="all_time_high_daily_avg">All-time high (daily avg.</string>


    <string-array name="timeArray">
        <item>24h</item>
        <item>7d</item>
        <item>30d</item>
        <item>1y</item>
        <item>5y</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="priceArray">
        <item>desc</item>
        <item>asc</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="marketCapArray">
        <item>desc</item>
        <item>asc</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ref">
        <item>USD</item>
        <item>BTC</item>
        <item>ETH</item>
        <item>HEX</item>
        <item>BNB</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>